jaybmunjani.com Curriculum Vitae Jay Munjani

Personal Informations

Name Jay Munjani

Address Ahmedabda - Gujarat - IN - 382350

Telephone/Mobile 909-9940-8806

E-mail jaybmunjani@gmail.com

Sex Male

Date of Birth 22/12/1998



Job Applied For

User Experince Researcher & Designer

Bio/Goals

I'm focused on creating meaningful experience through design. Also believe in approaching every question individually, combining various quantitative and qualitative methods to interpret human behaviours. Good as design thinker, Product designer, experience strategist, generative artist and human loving introvert. I've collaborated with a diverse group of product teams to create human centered product.

Apart from this i really love mountains, biking, hiking, gadgets and exploring technogies. I enjoy seeing things from a fresh perspective:)

Education

2021-Present Master of Design in User Experince and User Interface

Gujarat University Design School - Ahmedabad, Gujarat, IN 380009

2016–2020 Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Engineering

Silver Oak University - Ahmedabad, Gujarat, IN 380005

2014–2016 11-12th Science - Maths (PCM)

Presidency School - Surat, Gujarat, IN 395003

Job History

2019-Present UX/UI Designer

Freelancer Remote (WFH) - Ahmedabad, Gujarat, IN

Created new design themes for Ages of yoga and Decor. Participated in Research and Designing of Mobile and Web application for key clients under direction of Head & Tech Department. (*Freelance with collage*)

Key Achievements • Recognized for new and different concept logo,

- Praised by Ages of yoga team for dynamic dashboard design.

2020-2021 UX designer

Universal Software WFO - Ahmedabad, Gujarat, IN 380015

Planned and designed Application and Admin layout as requested by Core Team.

Key Achievements • Project is researched & designed single handedly

· Designed Super app for the first time,

Till 2019 Maker

EnCube Labs WFO - Gandhinagar, Gujarat, IN 382421

Manage and coordinate Education related maker activity projects from concept through completion. Work closely with students to create vision, conceive designs, and consistently make new things and execute ideas. Effectively tought student about Design thinking activity using Hardware, software and other resources.

Key Achievements Successfully organised makerfest and other events.

Successfully mentee students for theire ideas and goals.

Personal Skills

Mother tongue(s) Gujarati /Hindi

Other language(s) English

Soft Skills

- Communication/ Empathy/ Observation/ Problem Solving/ Neutrality
- Research Strategy and Design/ Critical Thinking
- Managment/ Collaboration/ Strategy
- · Leadership/ Teaching/ Mentoring

Methods

i worked with

User Experince Research, Design Research, A/B Testing, Interview (Moderated and Unmoderated), Usability Testing, Surveys, Card soriting, Focus Groups, Heuristic Evaluation, Prototyping, Remote Research, Field study, Statistical /Thematic/ Content Analysis, Tree Testing, Requirement gathering, Task Analysis, Heuristic evaluation, Information Architecture, Remote Research, Ethnographic Research

Technical Skills

Platforms Mac OS 10.15.4 (and previous versions) - Windows 10 (and previous versions).

Research software Miro, FigJam, Mural, Flowmap, Lucidchart, Hotjar, ATLAS.ti, UserZoom, UXArmy, UserTesting,

Optimal Workshop, Maze, Google form, Typeform, Survey Monkey, Loop11, Google meet/Hangout,

Google optimize, Usability hub

Design Software Adobe Creative Suite (XD, Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator, Acrobat, Lightroom, Dreamweaver)

Figma, Sketch, Framer, InVision, UXPin, Affinity designer, ProtoPie, Marvel, Balsamiq

Markup Language(s) HTLM /CSS /Bootstrap (Basic of backend /Android /IOS /Versioning)

Certifications IDF, Google, Coursera, Udemy, Udacity, Futurelearn, HCI IIT Bombay, Enterprise design thinking IBM

Microblogging https://www.instagram.com/kalpayita.in/

Achievements Participant at Spark AR program by Facebook SOI

Mentor at CODE19

- Mentor at Natinoal innovation workshop TechTop 2018
- Mentor at Tinkerfest delhi 2017
- Participant at MIT IIT Make in India 1 Month Bootcamp 2017
- 1st Price in Tic-Tech-Toe HackAThon
- 1st Price in Paper Presentaion GTU Techfest 2018



Page 2 - 4